Mss.Rec.85 Mss.Rec.85
American Philosophical Society
Malecite stories
1972
Mss.Rec.85
American Philosophical Society
6.0 Reel(s)
Multiple unidentified stories and speech given in Malecite-Passamaquody only from multiple consultants. Recorded in 1972, in Kingsclear, Oromocto, and St. Marys, New Brunswick.
6 sound tape reels, (5 hr., 35 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 2 tracks, mono; 5 in.
Polchic, Arthur
Polchic, Margaret
Polchic, Solomon
Szábo, László
Toomah, Madeleine
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by László Szábo in 1972 (Acc. 1972 593r). This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
Malecite Indians--Folklore; Passamaquoddy language; Passamaquoddy language--Texts; Sound recordings
- Audio recordings
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:29:12; Szabó, László; Toomah, Madeleine
    Scope and Contents note
    Multiple unidentified texts in Malecite-Passamaquody only.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Sound tape reel) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Kingsclear (N.B.); Passamaquoddy language--Texts
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:23:06; Polchic, Arthur; Szabó, László
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:31:37; Polchic, Margaret; Szabó, László
    Multiple unidentified texts in Malecite-Passamaquody only. Contains persistent sound distortion due to the microphone being placed too close to the speaker.
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 02-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:17:50; Paul, Mr.; Szabó, László
    Oromocto (N.B.); Passamaquoddy language--Texts
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 02-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:34; Szabó, László; Toomah, Madeleine
    Multiple unidentified texts in Malecite-Passamaquody only. Contains occasional sound distortion due to the microphone being placed too close to the speaker.
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:28:54; Polchic, Solomon; Szabó, László
    Passamaquoddy language--Texts; St. Marys (N.B.)
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:29:10; Szabó, László; Toomah, Madeleine
    Multiple unidentified texts in Malecite-Passamaquody only. Includes a brief period of singing from 17:51 to 18:17.
    Kingsclear (N.B.); Malecite Indians--Music; Passamaquoddy language--Texts
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:27:39; Polchic, Solomon; Szabó, László
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 04-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:31:28; Polchic, Solomon; Szabó, László
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:25:46; Polchic, Solomon; Szabó, László
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 05-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:28:07; Polchic, Arthur; Szabó, László
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 06-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:30:53; Polchic, Margaret; Szabó, László
  - Malecite Stories, 1972; 06-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:23:32; Polchic, Margaret; Szabó, László